STANDARD FOR LIFE
Early one morning, at The Synagogue Church Of All Nations,
this young lady arrived at the church gate in a wheelchair accompanied by her mother,
in desperate need of assistance.
Immediately responding to their cry for help,
the Emmanuel TV team interviewed them to find out what the problem was,
that had brought them all the way from Germany.
The young lady was brought into the church auditorium in a wheelchair,
unable to move around freely and accompanied by her mother.
She showed the team her identity card from Germany stating that she has been recognized,
by the German government as a disabled person.
The card reads, "The holder of this card is severely disabled."
Her mother also shows the team her daughter's medical report stating that she has been diagnosed,
with severe multiple sclerosis. Let's listen to them.
Good morning, I'm Marefe Wezolek and this is my daughter, Nicole Wezolek.
We come from Germany.
We were told that there will be a lot of people and we didn't want to be in the crowd.
That is why we came her earlier; we woke up at 2 o'clock and at 3 o'clock we started to come here.
So what is the problem that brought you here?
For one year, my daughter has been disabled.
She's using a wheelchair; she cannot do anything.
I must help her to either wash, cook her food and do everything.
She is 80 percent disabled.
She tried to look at the internet and she found The SCOAN.
That is why I have faith that she can be healed.
We can see that you have a document in front of you.
Can you please explain for us what this document says?
She has multiple sclerosis and it is becoming worse.
So because of the problem of multiple sclerosis,
your daughter has been using a wheelchair for the past year?
Yes, for a period of one year.
It started with numbness in her hands and then it spread over her whole body.
She cannot walk anymore without light.
She stumbled a lot of times on our staircase.
That was why we started to look for a solution.
This is a card for disabled people and it states that she is 80 percent disabled.
The "B" means she cannot do anything, without somebody assisting her.
She must use a wheelchair.
She is 80 percent disabled.
Can you tell us, how did you hear about The SCOAN and what prompted you to come?
She was the one who discovered The SCOAN through the internet and she told me about the ministry.
So, I watched the ministry's YouTube videos every day.
I have faith that Prophet T.B. Joshua is a man of God.
The disease is incurable; and it is getting worse every day.
I started to worry and that was why I said we should save money
to go to The SCOAN as fast as possible.
Hi! My name is Nicole Wezolek from Germany.
Can you please explain the problem that has brought you to The SCOAN today, so early this morning?
I am sick. I am disabled and I cannot walk; I use this wheelchair.
I searched on the internet and saw that
Prophet T.B Joshua can do everything with God.
So, I chose to come here.
We pray that God Almighty will heal you today during the service,
as the man of God comes to this service, in Jesus' Name.
Amen.
PROPHECY TIME
During The SCOAN Sunday Service, God uses Prophet T.B. Joshua to minister
prophecy, healing and deliverance to the people.
Among them is Nicole Wezolek and
her mother.
Prompted by the Holy Spirit, Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for her divine healing in Jesus' name.
Healing In Jesus' Name
There is a suicide spirit in the family.
Yes.
Everybody thinks of how to commit suicide.
Depression.
Yes, Man of God.
This one has it.
It is the second time she has escaped suicide.
Yes, it is true.
There was a time she set everything down to commit suicide.
She told me.
She told you?
Yes.
Prophecy Time
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healing In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I thank God and praise Him through Prophet T.B. Joshua for the deliverance and healing.
That's why we are here today, to testify to the goodness of God.
I am Marefe Wezolek from Germany.
This is my daughter Nicole.
Last week, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied that in the family, there was a spirit of depression and suicide.
That is true because when I was pregnant, I sensed this spirit always following me.
I was alone but I prayed to God.
It was only a few years ago that I detected that it was in the family with the children growing up.
We would quarrel and have misunderstandings in the family.
My daughter started to wear black clothes and separated from the group.
I could not understand her - that's why I prayed to God.
Just a year ago, she told me that she had numbness in her hands.
In one year, what started in the hands spread to the whole body - 100 percent numbness.
She could not walk. We went from
one doctor to another.
She had infusions of cortisone.
Because of the last infusion, she was already
very sad and afraid of another infusion.
So, I said that this is a time you have to pray to God for guidance.
That is why we are here.
Madam, after the man of God gave the message of prophecy concerning your daughter,
tell us what happened next.
After the prophecy and the deliverance, the effect was immediate.
She told me, "Mama, I can sense already. I can feel my hands and feet, and I can walk!
Praise God!" I was shocked
because she was healed instantly.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Before, she was wearing black clothes and going to the graveyard almost every day.
I asked her why and sensed that it was no longer normal;
that's why I prayed that God would guide her.
Was she cheerful, how did she relate with you as a mother and people around the community?
There was no good communication in the house; there were always misunderstandings.
Since after the prophecy and deliverance last Sunday, can you tells us the changes
you have seen in her attitude, and approach to people?
There are very big changes, physically and spiritually.
Is she happier now?
She's happy not only because of the healing but also because of the Spirit-filled environment.
Hallelujah! Once again, let's clap for Jesus Christ!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Nicole Wezolek from Germany and this is my mother.
T.B. Joshua prophesied to me last Sunday
that I had a suicidal spirit inside me
and depression, which was also in the family.
That was true because I wanted to kill myself two times but I didn't do it.
I had numbness all over my body; I couldn't feel my body anymore.
I couldn't walk; I had to use the wheelchair.
After T.B. Joshua touched me, I can feel and walk again.
It was so nice. I thank T.B. Joshua for
this amazing gift.
I thank God for the wonderful miracle.
Thank you.
Nicole Wezolek & Mother
Healing Testimony
Let us clap for Jesus Christ!
I was very depressed and sad all the time;
I didn't know why.
I thought people were angry with me but it was not so.
I am now happy that I can walk and feel again.
What about the numbness you used to feel?
The numbness is gone; I can feel my body one hundred percent!
Thank God! Praise God!
Wow! Let us clap for Jesus Christ!
The next day, Nicole Wezolek and her mother came back to The SCOAN to testify to her instant healing
from the problem of severe multiple sclerosis that had confined her to a wheelchair.
Nicole Wezolek
Healed Of Multiple Sclerosis In Jesus' Name
No Longer Uses A Wheelchair
My name is Nicole Wezolek and I'm from Germany.
Could you please tell us the problem that
brought you here to The SCOAN?
I came here because I was disabled
and I could not walk.
I used a wheelchair before.
So, before you came here, you had to make use of this wheelchair to be able to move around?
Yes, of course.
Last Sunday, I was sitting there and my mother sitting on the next chair.
Prophet T.B. Joshua came and prophesied that I had a spirit of suicide in my body.
He touched me and healed me, in Jesus' name.
Since then, I can walk.
I can feel everything in my body.
Before, I had numbness of my whole body
but now, I have feeling.
I no longer have to use this wheelchair.
Wow! So, you mean to say that you no longer need to use this wheelchair at all?
That you're completely healed in Jesus' name.
Yes, I no longer have to use this anymore.
I can walk!
So you mean to say that you no longer have those
suicidal thoughts anymore?
No, it's gone.
Amen. We thank God for this wonderful healing and deliverance that you have received.
Proving her complete healing, Nicole excitedly runs and jumps;
the numbness and pains are things of the past.
When Jesus Christ heals you, He heals you effectually.
He heals you completely.
Thank You, Jesus!
I am healed!
I thank God for healing my daughter.
I don't have to assist or help her anymore.
We don't need this wheelchair anymore.
I thank God for the deliverance and healing
through Prophet T.B Joshua.
To all the staff of the SCOAN -
thank you very much!
Thank You, Jesus!
After giving her awesome testimony,
Nicole Wezolek and her mother prepare to embark on their journey back to Germany.
Let's listen to them as they share their experience.
My name is Marefe Wezolek. I'm a professional nurse.
Today, we are leaving here for Germany.
This is my daughter Nicole Wezolek.
We are happy for everything -
for the healing and deliverance.
Thank you so much. Praise God!
Mrs Marefe Wezolek & Daughter
Germany
The man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua said that we should present you with this cash gift of 2000 USD
to support you and your daughter.
Oh my God! I am overwhelmed.
Thank you so much.
I didn't expect it.
Thank you very much, Prophet Joshua.
It's overwhelming!
This is for you and your daughter, to support your daughter from here on out.
In addition to that, the man of God also said we should present you with these five Morning Waters
and two booklets so you can continue to pray and minister it, in Jesus' name.
We believe the best is yet to come.
Thank you very much!
Praise God! Thank You, Jesus!
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
God bless you all.
Thank you!
Thank you very much. It is overwhelming.
I am touched with all your help.
Nicole Wezolek & Her Mother Return
To Germany Happy, Healed & Restored
RV: Mel Flowers 19/04/2019